



+420601510102



michalvesely4321@gmail.com



Padelky 1240/32, Rohatec



20/11/1992

www.linkedin.com/in/michal-vesely

Skills

- Microsoft Office
- Web development
- VS Code
- HTML
- **CSS**
- **JavaScript**
- **Problem-solving**
- Teamwork
- Communication
- **Native Czech**
- Fluent English

Education

2008 - 2012

High School of Chemistry

2017 - 2018

Kaplan International English

2019 - 2021

- **Business and Management**
- Diploma of business
- Advanced Diploma of business

2023

Programming course, ECDL

Michal Vesely

About me

My name is Michal Vesely and I am originally from the Czech Republic. I am passionate and interested in working as a web developer. I do enjoy working with computers especially HTML CSS in Visual Studio Code and keep improving up my coding skills. I have motivation to learn new things and make use of my experience. I am fluent in English, so I have no problem communicating with anyone. In my free time I like to play the guitar, hanging out with friends and spending time with my family.

Work Experience

2013

Kindergarden Rohatec: Czech Republic part-time

- Parenting support
- **Events planning**
- Officework (Excel)

2014-2016

IZOS: Production of insulated glass - Czech Republic {Office work}

- Organizing international orders and distribution
- using computer software (Microsoft Office)

2017-2023

Uber Eats: Western Australia part-time job (student)

Food delivery – Perth City in Western Australia